{
    "subject": "resource/Norman_Borlaug",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthYear",
    "object": "1914",
    "human_readable": "Norman Borlaug was born in 1914.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9194723963737488,
            "question": "In what year was Norman Borlaug born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8740772008895874,
            "question": "Where was Norman Borlaug born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5853943228721619,
            "question": "What is Norman Borlaug known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4744735658168793,
            "question": "What is Norman Borlaug's legacy?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39977094531059265,
            "question": "Which field of study was Norman Borlaug involved in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.36014190316200256,
            "question": "What impact did Norman Borlaug have on the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2821689546108246,
            "question": "Did Norman Borlaug make any significant contributions to agriculture?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.25107526779174805,
            "question": "What were some of the challenges faced by Norman Borlaug in his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.250453382730484,
            "question": "What awards or recognitions did Norman Borlaug receive?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1542655974626541,
            "question": "How did Norman Borlaug's work impact global food security?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Norman Borlaug was born in 1914.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6898_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What awards or recognitions did Norman Borlaug receive?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6898_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What were some of the challenges faced by Norman Borlaug in his work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6898_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Norman Borlaug make any significant contributions to agriculture?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6898_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6898_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6898_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6898_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6898_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6898_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6898_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6898_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6898_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6898_84.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6898_85.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which consistently state that Norman Ernest Borlaug was born on March 25, 1914."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}